kyozou.com 2013-05-09

# Privacy Statement

Kyozou Inc. ( **Kyozou** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

#### TEN PRINCIPLES TO COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Kyozou subscribes to the 10 Principles set out by the Canadian Standards Association with respect to Personal Information:

**Accountability**  Kyozou is responsible for personal information under its control and shall designate an individual or individuals who are accountable for the organization's compliance with the following principles.

**Identifying Purposes**  The purposes for which personal information is collected shall be identified by Kyozou at or before the time the information is collected.

**Consent:**  The knowledge and consent of the individual are required for the collection, use or disclosure of personal information, except when inappropriate.

**Limiting Collection:** The collection of personal information shall be limited to that which is necessary for the purposes identified by Kyozou.  Information shall be collected by fair and lawful means.

**Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention:** Personal information shall not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by the law.  Personal information shall be retained only as long as necessary for fulfillment of those purposes.

**Accuracy:** Personal information shall be as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.

**Safeguards:** Personal information shall be protected by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.

**Openness:** Kyozou shall make readily available to individuals specific information about its policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

**Individual Access:** Upon request, an individual shall be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of his or her personal information and shall be given access to that information. An individual shall be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate.

**Challenging Compliance:** An individual shall be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with the above principles to the designated individual or individuals responsible for Kyozous compliance with these principles.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service you requested. When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. We don't collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website.  Like many other commercial websites, the Kyozou website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site (which is described below in more detail).

Your personal information may be collected when you register and/or enter into an agreement for the provision of services, which include, but are not limited to, marketplace management system, on-line inventory and retail management systems and product shipping management systems by Kyozou or any other services which Kyozou may, in the future, provide to consumers of its services (collectively, the  **Services** ), or in any other way listed in this Privacy Policy.  Kyozou may collect and disclose this personal information for the purpose of providing these Services, including, but not limited to, setting up an Account for you in order to use Kyozous Site and Services.

Users of the Kyozou software ( **Users** ) may, from time to time, collect personal information from their customers in order to facilitate and/or complete transactions between them.  This information is collected by the User and is stored in Kyozous secure database for the exclusive use of that User only.  Kyozou only provides the means for the User to collect this information from its customers.  This information may be used by the User to complete certain transactions which include, but is not limited to, shipping products to its customer and handling and addressing warranty and Return Merchandise Authorization issues, as well as any other lawful purposes.  Kyozou does not monitor its Users collection, use and disclosure of personal information of its customers.  Should a Users customer have any questions regarding the use of their personal information by that User, they should contact the User directly.  Kyozous use of any personal information stored in its database is governed by this Privacy Policy.

You register to participate in an online survey, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or you submit an entry for a sweepstakes or other promotions, or when you submit your information to Kyozou for any other reason. From time to time, Kyozou receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Kyozou only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws.  If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information, within the Kyozou organization, to our affiliates, subsidiaries and any other related corporations ( **Related Companies** ).

## COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGY

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of Kyozou's website uses cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Kyozou's website if you do so. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through our website.

## INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Kyozou will use its best efforts to protect the following: i) your personal information; ii) your financial information; and iii) any other information, the collection and disclosure of which would constitute an offence under Privacy Protection legislation in force from time to time in the Province of Ontario and/or Canada (collectively, the  **Protected Information** ).  The Protected Information is never shared outside of Kyozou and its Related Companies without your consent.  Kyozou will only disclose the Protected Information in the following circumstances: i) in accordance with the purposes for which it was collected; ii) when Kyozou deems it is necessary to disclose the Protected Information to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; and/or iii) under conditions explained below.

Inside Kyozou, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in Canada or any other country where Kyozou and its Related Companies are located.

## DATA SECURITY

Kyozou safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our websites, Kyozou uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

## CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

Our websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 18. Kyozou does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for personal information.

## THIRD PARTY SITES

Kyozou website may contain links to other sites. Kyozou does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Kyozou will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at:[ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy1327%20=%20'info'%20+%20'@';%20addy1327%20=%20addy1327%20+%20'kyozou'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy1327%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy1327\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry)[info@kyozou.com](mailto:info@kyozou.com).
